<u>btong@berkeley.edu</u> +1 (925) 577-6826 btong.me

BRYAN TONG STUDENT / ENTREPRENEUR

Summary

A creative, ambitious student and entrepreneur with an interest in consumer technology, business, and VR/AR science. Currently studying Cognitive Science with a focus on Human-Computer Interaction at University of California, Berkeley. Possesses real-world business experience through founding MIRAI Apparel and working with various project teams in technology-related fields. Holds an additional 6 years' experience in UI/UX, contracting, and marketing.

Experience

KiteLion Games, LLCCo-Publisher, Lead Designer

2015 - current CA, MD Part-time

An ongoing project in collaboration with KiteLion Games. Codeveloping and publishing Sunset Brawlers, a mobile 2D fighting game. In charge of branding, UI/UX, game design, and web design. Featured in Technical.ly, showcased at Gamescape, and recently IGDA DC. Gained valuable knowledge of Unity, C#, net-code, and version control from this project.

http://sunsetbrawlers.com/

Agora Ventures, LLCSoftware / UX Contractor

2015 Remote Work Part-time

Worked with a small team of contractors to produce an educational video game for use in Maryland school system's history classes as an alternate teaching method. Our entire product, a card-based game for classroom tablets, was built in Unity over the span of eight weeks. Gained skills of UI/UX in Unity (C#) and mastery of Adobe Creative Suite.

Experience (cont.)

MIRAI Apparel

Founder / CEO

2012 – 2014 Pleasanton, CA Full-time

Designed high-end clothing, primarily of urban/streetwear styles. Worked with American Apparel and local screen printers to produce entirely American manufactured apparel. Oversaw all aspects of the company, ranging from product design, website code, and school marketing teams. With launch of first product line, local and viral marketing generated brand recognition by tens of thousands of individuals and generating profit of high thousands within weeks of first product sales.

Education

University of California, Berkeley

2015 - 2019

Bachelor's Degree, Cognitive Science Focus: Human-Computer Interaction

Member of Cognitive Science Student Association, Virtual Reality @ Berkeley

Skills

Python
Unity
C#
Version Control (Mercurial, Git)
HTML5 / CSS
Adobe Creative Suite

Proficient Fluent Proficient

> Fluent Fluent